venture-encoding.com 2013-12-06

# Venture - Privacy Policy

At www.venture-encoding.com, we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned about privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to let you know what kind of information we collect, how we use it, with whom it may be shared, what choices you have regarding our use of your information, and how you may review and change some of the data you provide to us. Our practices comply with all applicable U.S. laws and requirements.

We are located in the United States and this is a U.S.-based web site. By using this site, you agree to the transfer of your personal information to or within the United States.

As we continue to develop our web site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we offer, this policy likely will change. When we change it, we will post the change(s) on our web site. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate online notice to you.

#### What Information Do We Collect and How Do We Use It?

#### • Personal Information

We may collect various types of personal information from you, depending upon how you use our site. The categories of personal information we collect may include: 

| 

  1. Your first and last name
  2. A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town.
  3. Your e-mail address.
  4. Your telephone number.
  5. If you make a purchase on our site, your credit card number and related information.

---|---  
  
We may combine the information we collect from you with information we receive from you offline. We may also receive information about you from other sources, including, for example, address update services.

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for products and services; (2) to provide you with targeted offers and advertising on the site; (3) to contact you with information and promotional materials and offers from our company as well as from our subsidiaries, affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties; (4) to contact you; (5) to review site usage and operations; (6) to address problems with the site, our business or our products and services; and (7) to protect the security or integrity of the site and our business.

#### • Non-Personal Information

We, or third-party service providers acting on our behalf, may use cookies or web beacons on our site. A cookie is a small text file that may be stored on the hard drive of your computer when you access the site. A web beacon is an electronic image used to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page. We may use cookies and web beacons to collect non-personal information from you, including your IP address, browser type, the time and length of your visit, the pages of the site you visit and other clickstream data. This information may be used in order to: (1) remember the products in your shopping cart; (2) recognize you when you return to the site; (3) improve and personalize your experience on our site; (4) provide you with customized advertising; and (5) monitor site usage and analyze the behavior of site visitors. We do not collect any personal information through our use of cookies and web beacons, and we do not combine the non-personal information we collect through them with any of your personal information.

You may decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on our site. You also may be able to make some web beacons unusable by rejecting cookies. Check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

#### Do We Share Your Information?

We may transfer or otherwise disclose information collected from and about you to the following entities for the following purposes: (1) to our service providers, suppliers and business associates, if the disclosure will enable them to fulfill your request for products or services from us for another vendor on our site; (2) to our service providers and business associates, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (3) to our affiliates and other third parties so that they may contact you with marketing offers of their own; (4) to other companies, credit bureaus or government agencies in connection with issues related to fraud, credit or debt collection; (5) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our site Terms of Use, of the law or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (6) to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (7) if our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets.

Any personal information or content that you voluntarily upload or submit for posting to the site becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. It is in violation of the site's Terms of Use for you to post any content that requests personally identifiable information.

#### Can I Change My Information?

You may change or update your personal information by sending an email to [info@venturesolutions.com](mailto:info@venturesolutions.com). Please include "Change My Information" in the subject line.

#### What About Information About Children?

We do not direct the site to, nor do we knowingly collect personal information from, children under thirteen.

#### Security

We have taken certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from site visitors.

#### Third Party Websites

The site may contain links to third-party websites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on these sites. Accordingly, we recommend that you review the privacy policy posted on any site that you may access through our site.

#### Contact Us

Thank you for visiting our site. If you have any questions or comments about this policy, please send an email to: [info@venturesolutions.com](mailto:info@venturesolutions.com). Please include "Question or Comment" in the subject line.
